Arno Verhoeven

SentiOne | Social listening & engagement tool for better insights and reputation management

Summary

Right now I am primarily focused on the introduction of SentiOne to the Benelux. SentiOne is a successful scale up offering high end social and online monitoring tools. For professionals who seek an easy to use and flexible tool but also demand the best data sets, this is THE tool.

About me:

With over 25 years of experience in marketing and advertising, and over 20 years of experience in online business I consider myself a no nonsense strategist and entrepreneur. I help clients to strengthen and expand their (online) market positions. Together with clients I love to strip challenges to the core. Finding the essence, and from there create new directions, opportunities and solutions. Straight forward, highly motivated, informal, never holding back and constructive.

Experience

Director at SentiOne Nederland October 2014 - Present

SentiOne is a big data company who helps organizations

- getting the right picture of what target groups are saying online (analytics),
- and achieving a stronger engagement with the market through online discussions (webcare).

We track global and local brands and measure consumer opinions and activities in social media and online platforms. With our smart tools our clients gain stronger insights and analytics that will help them make better decisions.

POWERFUL and EASY:

We believe that the key to success for a tool is a golden combination of ease of use and powerful data. Our tools are a joy to work with while still giving the very best results.

With SentiOne you can listen to microblogs, blogs, internet forums, portals, review sites and social networks in over 23 European languages. All our languages are supported by native speaking analysts. We do all data harvesting ourselves, store it on our own servers where we unleash our own self learning algorithms on it. With this data we can offer you a wide range of options, such as buzz, automatic sentiment and gender analysis, real time engagement, reach, advanced queries, cooperation options for teams, reporting and much more.

Today, SentiOne is listening online in 26 European countries.

We work with over 500 large and medium companies among them Huawei, Procter & Gamble, McDonald's, Nike, Unilever, Beiersdorf, Tesco, Starcom, Mindshare, Mediacom, Saatchi & Saatchi and Ogilvy and Mather.

www.sentione.nl

My responsibilities are:

- Strategic Consulting, including business plan & sales strategy development and implementation
- Key Customer Acquisition
- Sales team management, training and recruitment
- Business relations development with Key Customers
- Sales budget preparation and implementation
- Reporting results to the Supervisory Board

Owner at Beachhead

December 2011 - Present

Beachhead Online (established 1993), agency for online communications specialized in:

- . marketing and online strategies
- . websites and webapplications

Bestuurslid - communicatie en sponsorwerving at Eiffel Swimmers NZE December 2008 - January 2013 (4 years 2 months)

Owner

June 1994 - December 2011 (17 years 7 months)

Reclameteam Verhoeven (established 1969), agency for marketing communications specialized in:

- . marketing and communications strategies
- . brand building
- . design
- . productions and project management

Account Manager

September 1991 - June 1994 (2 years 10 months)

Education

Avans Hogeschool Breda ba, marketing, 1986 - 1991

Arno Verhoeven

SentiOne | Social listening & engagement tool for better insights and reputation management



Contact Arno on LinkedIn